<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<zabbix_export>
    <version>6.0</version>
    <templates>
        <template>
            <uuid>cb1df4cbef9847a6bcb08cbbdbcad73a</uuid>
            <template>host-A</template>
            <name>host-A</name>
            <description>Template built by SNMPWALK2ZABBIX script from https://github.com/Sean-Bradley/SNMPWALK2ZABBIX</description>
            <groups>
                <group>
                    <name>Templates</name>
                </group>
            </groups>
            <items>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>4ba33b0cb3634158a169e3f62704bc5b</uuid>
                    <name>sysDescr</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.1.1.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.sysDescr.0</key>                    
                    <value_type>CHAR</value_type>
                    <description>A textual description of the entity. This value should include the full name and version identification of the system's hardware type, software operating-system, and networking software.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>45257a3441354952975527dae1f5a39c</uuid>
                    <name>sysObjectID</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.1.2.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.sysObjectID.0</key>                    
                    <value_type>CHAR</value_type>
                    <description>The vendor's authoritative identification of the network management subsystem contained in the entity. This value is allocated within the SMI enterprises subtree (1.3.6.1.4.1) and provides an easy and unambiguous means for determining `what kind of box' is being managed. For example, if vendor `Flintstones, Inc.' was assigned the subtree 1.3.6.1.4.1.424242, it could assign the identifier 1.3.6.1.4.1.424242.1.1 to its `Fred Router'.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>c0e0b0fe073d483eba81db5dc5b230bb</uuid>
                    <name>sysUpTimeInstance</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.1.3.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>DISMAN-EVENT-MIB.sysUpTimeInstance</key>
                    <description>DISMAN-EVENT-MIB::sysUpTimeInstance
sysUpTimeInstance OBJECT-TYPE
  -- FROM	DISMAN-EVENT-MIB
::= { iso(1) org(3) dod(6) internet(1) mgmt(2) mib-2(1) system(1) sysUpTime(3) 0 }
</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>825488c2959d45eaa2e86d8a3d55b462</uuid>
                    <name>sysContact</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.1.4.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.sysContact.0</key>                    
                    <value_type>CHAR</value_type>
                    <description>The textual identification of the contact person for this managed node, together with information on how to contact this person. If no contact information is known, the value is the zero-length string.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>ed7cb74916c74d58a569e62585df57b2</uuid>
                    <name>sysName</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.1.5.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.sysName.0</key>                    
                    <value_type>CHAR</value_type>
                    <description>An administratively-assigned name for this managed node. By convention, this is the node's fully-qualified domain name. If the name is unknown, the value is the zero-length string.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>8f84e932e0b94cd99a4f7fd3a4b8eacf</uuid>
                    <name>sysLocation</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.1.6.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.sysLocation.0</key>                    
                    <value_type>CHAR</value_type>
                    <description>The physical location of this node (e.g., 'telephone closet, 3rd floor'). If the location is unknown, the value is the zero-length string.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>6dd94a50cf4048e6a45f57d4868e3482</uuid>
                    <name>sysServices</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.1.7.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.sysServices.0</key>                    
                    <value_type>FLOAT</value_type>
                    <description>A value which indicates the set of services that this entity may potentially offer. The value is a sum. This sum initially takes the value zero. Then, for each layer, L, in the range 1 through 7, that this node performs transactions for, 2 raised to (L - 1) is added to the sum. For example, a node which performs only routing functions would have a value of 4 (2^(3-1)). In contrast, a node which is a host offering application services would have a value of 72 (2^(4-1) + 2^(7-1)). Note that in the context of the Internet suite of protocols, values should be calculated accordingly: layer functionality 1 physical (e.g., repeaters) 2 datalink/subnetwork (e.g., bridges) 3 internet (e.g., supports the IP) 4 end-to-end (e.g., supports the TCP) 7 applications (e.g., supports the SMTP) For systems including OSI protocols, layers 5 and 6 may also be counted.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>9e80365fe7674f23807d03d1401d0dd6</uuid>
                    <name>sysORLastChange</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.1.8.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.sysORLastChange.0</key>
                    <description>The value of sysUpTime at the time of the most recent change in state or value of any instance of sysORID.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>e4fef98cdc1c4fa19bdc789064a1c260</uuid>
                    <name>ifNumber</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.1.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IF-MIB.ifNumber.0</key>                    
                    <value_type>FLOAT</value_type>
                    <description>The number of network interfaces (regardless of their current state) present on this system.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>c65eca3ca3134adf873a054a26e301ef</uuid>
                    <name>ipForwarding</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.1.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.ipForwarding.0</key>                    
                    <value_type>FLOAT</value_type>
                    <description>The indication of whether this entity is acting as an IPv4 router in respect to the forwarding of datagrams received by, but not addressed to, this entity. IPv4 routers forward datagrams. IPv4 hosts do not (except those source-routed via the host). When this object is written, the entity should save the change to non-volatile storage and restore the object from non-volatile storage upon re-initialization of the system. Note: a stronger requirement is not used because this object was previously defined.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>22ff81a5515344b3b8efdda3d845de17</uuid>
                    <name>ipDefaultTTL</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.2.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.ipDefaultTTL.0</key>                    
                    <value_type>FLOAT</value_type>
                    <description>The default value inserted into the Time-To-Live field of the IPv4 header of datagrams originated at this entity, whenever a TTL value is not supplied by the transport layer protocol. When this object is written, the entity should save the change to non-volatile storage and restore the object from non-volatile storage upon re-initialization of the system. Note: a stronger requirement is not used because this object was previously defined.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>c6ebd31b73d04a5f8b126a93aef0b981</uuid>
                    <name>ipInReceives</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.3.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.ipInReceives.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of input datagrams received from interfaces, including those received in error. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by ipSystemStatsInRecieves.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>4c2dc059e79543779727c2cdbb428d2f</uuid>
                    <name>ipInHdrErrors</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.4.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.ipInHdrErrors.0</key>
                    <description>The number of input datagrams discarded due to errors in their IPv4 headers, including bad checksums, version number mismatch, other format errors, time-to-live exceeded, errors discovered in processing their IPv4 options, etc. This object has been deprecated as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by ipSystemStatsInHdrErrors.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>01dda5af01b549de9cb568b99fe92c33</uuid>
                    <name>ipInAddrErrors</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.5.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.ipInAddrErrors.0</key>
                    <description>The number of input datagrams discarded because the IPv4 address in their IPv4 header's destination field was not a valid address to be received at this entity. This count includes invalid addresses (e.g., 0.0.0.0) and addresses of unsupported Classes (e.g., Class E). For entities which are not IPv4 routers, and therefore do not forward datagrams, this counter includes datagrams discarded because the destination address was not a local address. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by ipSystemStatsInAddrErrors.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>aade4bd81fe64b878b8ed233c722c93e</uuid>
                    <name>ipForwDatagrams</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.6.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.ipForwDatagrams.0</key>
                    <description>The number of input datagrams for which this entity was not their final IPv4 destination, as a result of which an attempt was made to find a route to forward them to that final destination. In entities which do not act as IPv4 routers, this counter will include only those packets which were Source-Routed via this entity, and the Source-Route option processing was successful. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by ipSystemStatsInForwDatagrams.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>21360d181b2f4f6c89e008469c42efb4</uuid>
                    <name>ipInUnknownProtos</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.7.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.ipInUnknownProtos.0</key>
                    <description>The number of locally-addressed datagrams received successfully but discarded because of an unknown or unsupported protocol. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by ipSystemStatsInUnknownProtos.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>0e1d4b5b51b546efbfd03f86a23c0276</uuid>
                    <name>ipInDiscards</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.8.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.ipInDiscards.0</key>
                    <description>The number of input IPv4 datagrams for which no problems were encountered to prevent their continued processing, but which were discarded (e.g., for lack of buffer space). Note that this counter does not include any datagrams discarded while awaiting re-assembly. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by ipSystemStatsInDiscards.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>365be8db5c4c46239ad0ed98f8af2ba7</uuid>
                    <name>ipInDelivers</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.9.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.ipInDelivers.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of input datagrams successfully delivered to IPv4 user-protocols (including ICMP). This object has been deprecated as a new IP version neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by ipSystemStatsIndelivers.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>81519925b06b40709ecce2caa5d19ea0</uuid>
                    <name>ipOutRequests</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.10.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.ipOutRequests.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of IPv4 datagrams which local IPv4 user protocols (including ICMP) supplied to IPv4 in requests for transmission. Note that this counter does not include any datagrams counted in ipForwDatagrams. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by ipSystemStatsOutRequests.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>f5a0b96da65947558935a5d0014011ad</uuid>
                    <name>ipOutDiscards</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.11.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.ipOutDiscards.0</key>
                    <description>The number of output IPv4 datagrams for which no problem was encountered to prevent their transmission to their destination, but which were discarded (e.g., for lack of buffer space). Note that this counter would include datagrams counted in ipForwDatagrams if any such packets met this (discretionary) discard criterion. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by ipSystemStatsOutDiscards.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>4174d880997f4f8aab18a7a5f4772c44</uuid>
                    <name>ipOutNoRoutes</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.12.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.ipOutNoRoutes.0</key>
                    <description>The number of IPv4 datagrams discarded because no route could be found to transmit them to their destination. Note that this counter includes any packets counted in ipForwDatagrams which meet this `no-route' criterion. Note that this includes any datagrams which a host cannot route because all of its default routers are down. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by ipSystemStatsOutNoRoutes.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>e8e0570ff35c401eb208657b10a96f6f</uuid>
                    <name>ipReasmTimeout</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.13.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.ipReasmTimeout.0</key>                    
                    <value_type>FLOAT</value_type>
                    <description>The maximum number of seconds that received fragments are held while they are awaiting reassembly at this entity.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>a19437816636481a994c62dabd2310d0</uuid>
                    <name>ipReasmReqds</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.14.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.ipReasmReqds.0</key>
                    <description>The number of IPv4 fragments received which needed to be reassembled at this entity. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by ipSystemStatsReasmReqds.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>a6524db7ba934fee88d4295860f83b22</uuid>
                    <name>ipReasmOKs</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.15.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.ipReasmOKs.0</key>
                    <description>The number of IPv4 datagrams successfully re-assembled. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by ipSystemStatsReasmOKs.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>772b7f05c567435a83c6f603043d56b2</uuid>
                    <name>ipReasmFails</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.16.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.ipReasmFails.0</key>
                    <description>The number of failures detected by the IPv4 re-assembly algorithm (for whatever reason: timed out, errors, etc). Note that this is not necessarily a count of discarded IPv4 fragments since some algorithms (notably the algorithm in RFC 815) can lose track of the number of fragments by combining them as they are received. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by ipSystemStatsReasmFails.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>6bbb7033c557444fbf70a03222ce0ba5</uuid>
                    <name>ipFragOKs</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.17.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.ipFragOKs.0</key>
                    <description>The number of IPv4 datagrams that have been successfully fragmented at this entity. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by ipSystemStatsOutFragOKs.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>545fd9a2cfba4d46aab55e4bd1cb50cd</uuid>
                    <name>ipFragFails</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.18.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.ipFragFails.0</key>
                    <description>The number of IPv4 datagrams that have been discarded because they needed to be fragmented at this entity but could not be, e.g., because their Don't Fragment flag was set. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by ipSystemStatsOutFragFails.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>49f1aec7cf884141bfb292cb81824a7e</uuid>
                    <name>ipFragCreates</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.19.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.ipFragCreates.0</key>
                    <description>The number of IPv4 datagram fragments that have been generated as a result of fragmentation at this entity. This object has been deprecated as a new IP version neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by ipSystemStatsOutFragCreates.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>93cd4caaf3e547d1a0a6ed3391a07eca</uuid>
                    <name>ipRoutingDiscards</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.23.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.ipRoutingDiscards.0</key>
                    <description>The number of routing entries which were chosen to be discarded even though they are valid. One possible reason for discarding such an entry could be to free-up buffer space for other routing entries. This object was defined in pre-IPv6 versions of the IP MIB. It was implicitly IPv4 only, but the original specifications did not indicate this protocol restriction. In order to clarify the specifications, this object has been deprecated and a similar, but more thoroughly clarified, object has been added to the IP-FORWARD-MIB.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>53b1a854876e4d06af8f0fd36947ae35</uuid>
                    <name>inetCidrRouteNumber</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.24.6.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-FORWARD-MIB.inetCidrRouteNumber.0</key>
                    <description>The number of current inetCidrRouteTable entries that are not invalid.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>8082209b0c204b15a12ad3c4c66b4053</uuid>
                    <name>ipv6IpForwarding</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.25.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.ipv6IpForwarding.0</key>                    
                    <value_type>FLOAT</value_type>
                    <description>The indication of whether this entity is acting as an IPv6 router on any interface in respect to the forwarding of datagrams received by, but not addressed to, this entity. IPv6 routers forward datagrams. IPv6 hosts do not (except those source-routed via the host). When this object is written, the entity SHOULD save the change to non-volatile storage and restore the object from non-volatile storage upon re-initialization of the system.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>a75b6267f7dc4ae1a1823d412c7a2fe0</uuid>
                    <name>ipv6IpDefaultHopLimit</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.26.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.ipv6IpDefaultHopLimit.0</key>                    
                    <value_type>FLOAT</value_type>
                    <description>The default value inserted into the Hop Limit field of the IPv6 header of datagrams originated at this entity whenever a Hop Limit value is not supplied by the transport layer protocol. When this object is written, the entity SHOULD save the change to non-volatile storage and restore the object from non-volatile storage upon re-initialization of the system.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>c36323bf6f834443a82f6bdc6f0c5f98</uuid>
                    <name>ipIfStatsTableLastChange</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.31.2.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.ipIfStatsTableLastChange.0</key>
                    <description>The value of sysUpTime on the most recent occasion at which a row in the ipIfStatsTable was added or deleted. If new objects are added to the ipIfStatsTable that require the ipIfStatsTableLastChange to be updated when they are modified, they must specify that requirement in their description clause.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>f424a847c19d40a5a74f4b1bfb77f6a1</uuid>
                    <name>ipAddressSpinLock</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.33.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.ipAddressSpinLock.0</key>                    
                    <value_type>FLOAT</value_type>
                    <description>An advisory lock used to allow cooperating SNMP managers to coordinate their use of the set operation in creating or modifying rows within this table. In order to use this lock to coordinate the use of set operations, managers should first retrieve ipAddressTableSpinLock. They should then determine the appropriate row to create or modify. Finally, they should issue the appropriate set command, including the retrieved value of ipAddressSpinLock. If another manager has altered the table in the meantime, then the value of ipAddressSpinLock will have changed, and the creation will fail as it will be specifying an incorrect value for ipAddressSpinLock. It is suggested, but not required, that the ipAddressSpinLock be the first var bind for each set of objects representing a 'row' in a PDU.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>ae645a6f07fd41cb8d6eea696a905fed</uuid>
                    <name>icmpInMsgs</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.1.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.icmpInMsgs.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of ICMP messages which the entity received. Note that this counter includes all those counted by icmpInErrors. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by icmpStatsInMsgs.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>3e12b3747995413aa7e174130620c53c</uuid>
                    <name>icmpInErrors</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.2.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.icmpInErrors.0</key>
                    <description>The number of ICMP messages which the entity received but determined as having ICMP-specific errors (bad ICMP checksums, bad length, etc.). This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by icmpStatsInErrors.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>56cc2b43b1ce47178b261874b95ac04f</uuid>
                    <name>icmpInDestUnreachs</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.3.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.icmpInDestUnreachs.0</key>
                    <description>The number of ICMP Destination Unreachable messages received. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by a column in the icmpMsgStatsTable.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>f5d62b5e449f44ea8545bf99e9f5d620</uuid>
                    <name>icmpInTimeExcds</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.4.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.icmpInTimeExcds.0</key>
                    <description>The number of ICMP Time Exceeded messages received. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by a column in the icmpMsgStatsTable.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>8a42181277fa4d5c96805cc96aece8f1</uuid>
                    <name>icmpInParmProbs</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.5.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.icmpInParmProbs.0</key>
                    <description>The number of ICMP Parameter Problem messages received. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by a column in the icmpMsgStatsTable.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>81b6e9d3913a48319ff0c7262c3598d2</uuid>
                    <name>icmpInSrcQuenchs</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.6.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.icmpInSrcQuenchs.0</key>
                    <description>The number of ICMP Source Quench messages received. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by a column in the icmpMsgStatsTable.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>5479b58d05224193842ee21f1e011775</uuid>
                    <name>icmpInRedirects</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.7.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.icmpInRedirects.0</key>
                    <description>The number of ICMP Redirect messages received. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by a column in the icmpMsgStatsTable.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>3e1ca74dd8b24108ac2c734fb5fd8e17</uuid>
                    <name>icmpInEchos</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.8.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.icmpInEchos.0</key>
                    <description>The number of ICMP Echo (request) messages received. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by a column in the icmpMsgStatsTable.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>971214cf96e24ce9922d9b43b4e48b56</uuid>
                    <name>icmpInEchoReps</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.9.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.icmpInEchoReps.0</key>
                    <description>The number of ICMP Echo Reply messages received. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by a column in the icmpMsgStatsTable.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>915159dbd43845e3ac70f858cb0efd81</uuid>
                    <name>icmpInTimestamps</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.10.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.icmpInTimestamps.0</key>
                    <description>The number of ICMP Timestamp (request) messages received. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by a column in the icmpMsgStatsTable.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>749b28e2bde7494d877fdbc6e1a44d24</uuid>
                    <name>icmpInTimestampReps</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.11.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.icmpInTimestampReps.0</key>
                    <description>The number of ICMP Timestamp Reply messages received. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by a column in the icmpMsgStatsTable.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>28cbe94af9854d56a80ebf7a8fd82de0</uuid>
                    <name>icmpInAddrMasks</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.12.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.icmpInAddrMasks.0</key>
                    <description>The number of ICMP Address Mask Request messages received. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by a column in the icmpMsgStatsTable.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>2d8eb051e31044afa970cd62c12c844e</uuid>
                    <name>icmpInAddrMaskReps</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.13.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.icmpInAddrMaskReps.0</key>
                    <description>The number of ICMP Address Mask Reply messages received. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by a column in the icmpMsgStatsTable.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>5aea18f2c16047f3914045783d6dbed0</uuid>
                    <name>icmpOutMsgs</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.14.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.icmpOutMsgs.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of ICMP messages which this entity attempted to send. Note that this counter includes all those counted by icmpOutErrors. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by icmpStatsOutMsgs.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>9ec4c9056fb94ce7ba2adeabe3883408</uuid>
                    <name>icmpOutErrors</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.15.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.icmpOutErrors.0</key>
                    <description>The number of ICMP messages which this entity did not send due to problems discovered within ICMP, such as a lack of buffers. This value should not include errors discovered outside the ICMP layer, such as the inability of IP to route the resultant datagram. In some implementations, there may be no types of error which contribute to this counter's value. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by icmpStatsOutErrors.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>285bf09b111244c7baa33233884c7019</uuid>
                    <name>icmpOutDestUnreachs</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.16.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.icmpOutDestUnreachs.0</key>
                    <description>The number of ICMP Destination Unreachable messages sent. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by a column in the icmpMsgStatsTable.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>485ebb0967c24213bc12b6d7b810032d</uuid>
                    <name>icmpOutTimeExcds</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.17.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.icmpOutTimeExcds.0</key>
                    <description>The number of ICMP Time Exceeded messages sent. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by a column in the icmpMsgStatsTable.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>1762ccb14d414e03b3e6fb30a1f14554</uuid>
                    <name>icmpOutParmProbs</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.18.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.icmpOutParmProbs.0</key>
                    <description>The number of ICMP Parameter Problem messages sent. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by a column in the icmpMsgStatsTable.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>66d00d837e704692bcedaad21cb4fd30</uuid>
                    <name>icmpOutSrcQuenchs</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.19.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.icmpOutSrcQuenchs.0</key>
                    <description>The number of ICMP Source Quench messages sent. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by a column in the icmpMsgStatsTable.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>ad5f5984f01f4a6b8e75f57676b30498</uuid>
                    <name>icmpOutRedirects</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.20.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.icmpOutRedirects.0</key>
                    <description>The number of ICMP Redirect messages sent. For a host, this object will always be zero, since hosts do not send redirects. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by a column in the icmpMsgStatsTable.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>baf2d6ba48314799b01041e992b645c8</uuid>
                    <name>icmpOutEchos</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.21.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.icmpOutEchos.0</key>
                    <description>The number of ICMP Echo (request) messages sent. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by a column in the icmpMsgStatsTable.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>b7ed5a9d4875408dabab5cdc4b44132e</uuid>
                    <name>icmpOutEchoReps</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.22.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.icmpOutEchoReps.0</key>
                    <description>The number of ICMP Echo Reply messages sent. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by a column in the icmpMsgStatsTable.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>d6f35809e07342a8a5e454a526364d96</uuid>
                    <name>icmpOutTimestamps</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.23.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.icmpOutTimestamps.0</key>
                    <description>The number of ICMP Timestamp (request) messages sent. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by a column in the icmpMsgStatsTable.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>5a5b8783f8ba4194a36d018ef66d2988</uuid>
                    <name>icmpOutTimestampReps</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.24.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.icmpOutTimestampReps.0</key>
                    <description>The number of ICMP Timestamp Reply messages sent. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by a column in the icmpMsgStatsTable.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>8c4e301144cf4a29a16b053e7db2c278</uuid>
                    <name>icmpOutAddrMasks</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.25.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.icmpOutAddrMasks.0</key>
                    <description>The number of ICMP Address Mask Request messages sent. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by a column in the icmpMsgStatsTable.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>87376bb9b41145b1b7aeac5aa06cb5a9</uuid>
                    <name>icmpOutAddrMaskReps</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.26.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IP-MIB.icmpOutAddrMaskReps.0</key>
                    <description>The number of ICMP Address Mask Reply messages sent. This object has been deprecated, as a new IP version-neutral table has been added. It is loosely replaced by a column in the icmpMsgStatsTable.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>f8eba12400084ff2be986425f8ba2fa6</uuid>
                    <name>tcpRtoAlgorithm</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.6.1.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>TCP-MIB.tcpRtoAlgorithm.0</key>                    
                    <value_type>FLOAT</value_type>
                    <description>The algorithm used to determine the timeout value used for retransmitting unacknowledged octets.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>b67ea5a1c2074ebd8a8bf17ae3f1cdf4</uuid>
                    <name>tcpRtoMin</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.6.2.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>TCP-MIB.tcpRtoMin.0</key>                    
                    <value_type>FLOAT</value_type>
                    <description>The minimum value permitted by a TCP implementation for the retransmission timeout, measured in milliseconds. More refined semantics for objects of this type depend on the algorithm used to determine the retransmission timeout; in particular, the IETF standard algorithm rfc2988(5) provides a minimum value.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>d58ad439be2047f5b021ac2fccfb582b</uuid>
                    <name>tcpRtoMax</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.6.3.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>TCP-MIB.tcpRtoMax.0</key>                    
                    <value_type>FLOAT</value_type>
                    <description>The maximum value permitted by a TCP implementation for the retransmission timeout, measured in milliseconds. More refined semantics for objects of this type depend on the algorithm used to determine the retransmission timeout; in particular, the IETF standard algorithm rfc2988(5) provides an upper bound (as part of an adaptive backoff algorithm).</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>b3b379e7313c49aebc9f4e000e69e76b</uuid>
                    <name>tcpMaxConn</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.6.4.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>TCP-MIB.tcpMaxConn.0</key>                    
                    <value_type>FLOAT</value_type>
                    <description>The limit on the total number of TCP connections the entity can support. In entities where the maximum number of connections is dynamic, this object should contain the value -1.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>0da35ef3a2ed4e1c8b8fff10200dfeea</uuid>
                    <name>tcpActiveOpens</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.6.5.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>TCP-MIB.tcpActiveOpens.0</key>
                    <description>The number of times that TCP connections have made a direct transition to the SYN-SENT state from the CLOSED state. Discontinuities in the value of this counter are indicated via discontinuities in the value of sysUpTime.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>74ac432bb51044c8a1e349f2e78da544</uuid>
                    <name>tcpPassiveOpens</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.6.6.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>TCP-MIB.tcpPassiveOpens.0</key>
                    <description>The number of times TCP connections have made a direct transition to the SYN-RCVD state from the LISTEN state. Discontinuities in the value of this counter are indicated via discontinuities in the value of sysUpTime.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>c1688d94183c4938971828689398e107</uuid>
                    <name>tcpAttemptFails</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.6.7.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>TCP-MIB.tcpAttemptFails.0</key>
                    <description>The number of times that TCP connections have made a direct transition to the CLOSED state from either the SYN-SENT state or the SYN-RCVD state, plus the number of times that TCP connections have made a direct transition to the LISTEN state from the SYN-RCVD state. Discontinuities in the value of this counter are indicated via discontinuities in the value of sysUpTime.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>beb759d3d2fd4a51892e4d632984c900</uuid>
                    <name>tcpEstabResets</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.6.8.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>TCP-MIB.tcpEstabResets.0</key>
                    <description>The number of times that TCP connections have made a direct transition to the CLOSED state from either the ESTABLISHED state or the CLOSE-WAIT state. Discontinuities in the value of this counter are indicated via discontinuities in the value of sysUpTime.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>39d9e7bc06c3437f96e41bb81972f063</uuid>
                    <name>tcpCurrEstab</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.6.9.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>TCP-MIB.tcpCurrEstab.0</key>
                    <description>The number of TCP connections for which the current state is either ESTABLISHED or CLOSE-WAIT.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>911ec8765de64f99a240b91fee9c5fbf</uuid>
                    <name>tcpInSegs</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.6.10.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>TCP-MIB.tcpInSegs.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of segments received, including those received in error. This count includes segments received on currently established connections. Discontinuities in the value of this counter are indicated via discontinuities in the value of sysUpTime.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>5f488b60820e4718ab88633c446abb6c</uuid>
                    <name>tcpOutSegs</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.6.11.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>TCP-MIB.tcpOutSegs.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of segments sent, including those on current connections but excluding those containing only retransmitted octets. Discontinuities in the value of this counter are indicated via discontinuities in the value of sysUpTime.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>5515b70e5dec40d2968590638352b66d</uuid>
                    <name>tcpRetransSegs</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.6.12.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>TCP-MIB.tcpRetransSegs.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of segments retransmitted; that is, the number of TCP segments transmitted containing one or more previously transmitted octets. Discontinuities in the value of this counter are indicated via discontinuities in the value of sysUpTime.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>7a7ee927371e4756b4590b6dc3075ae9</uuid>
                    <name>tcpInErrs</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.6.14.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>TCP-MIB.tcpInErrs.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of segments received in error (e.g., bad TCP checksums). Discontinuities in the value of this counter are indicated via discontinuities in the value of sysUpTime.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>190c2e996ec54a45a61cb4ac09cb8619</uuid>
                    <name>tcpOutRsts</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.6.15.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>TCP-MIB.tcpOutRsts.0</key>
                    <description>The number of TCP segments sent containing the RST flag. Discontinuities in the value of this counter are indicated via discontinuities in the value of sysUpTime.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>a5be8d88413b4fe9b771891ed15be963</uuid>
                    <name>udpInDatagrams</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.7.1.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>UDP-MIB.udpInDatagrams.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of UDP datagrams delivered to UDP users. Discontinuities in the value of this counter can occur at re-initialization of the management system, and at other times as indicated by discontinuities in the value of sysUpTime.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>39482a2f8bda47ceb03ba5f9d28e07e6</uuid>
                    <name>udpNoPorts</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.7.2.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>UDP-MIB.udpNoPorts.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of received UDP datagrams for which there was no application at the destination port. Discontinuities in the value of this counter can occur at re-initialization of the management system, and at other times as indicated by discontinuities in the value of sysUpTime.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>5c7d32fb52b1491a9dbfb9095b6c3600</uuid>
                    <name>udpInErrors</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.7.3.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>UDP-MIB.udpInErrors.0</key>
                    <description>The number of received UDP datagrams that could not be delivered for reasons other than the lack of an application at the destination port. Discontinuities in the value of this counter can occur at re-initialization of the management system, and at other times as indicated by discontinuities in the value of sysUpTime.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>db147f2ec1b34cfd92343cfd20be96ba</uuid>
                    <name>udpOutDatagrams</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.7.4.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>UDP-MIB.udpOutDatagrams.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of UDP datagrams sent from this entity. Discontinuities in the value of this counter can occur at re-initialization of the management system, and at other times as indicated by discontinuities in the value of sysUpTime.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>662f8bb2003b439191014b253be84845</uuid>
                    <name>snmpInPkts</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.11.1.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.snmpInPkts.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of messages delivered to the SNMP entity from the transport service.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>87cbea7f67dd437aa0e73c6288b39ca4</uuid>
                    <name>snmpOutPkts</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.11.2.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.snmpOutPkts.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of SNMP Messages which were passed from the SNMP protocol entity to the transport service.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>d67628c28640460da86407e801a453ba</uuid>
                    <name>snmpInBadVersions</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.11.3.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.snmpInBadVersions.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of SNMP messages which were delivered to the SNMP entity and were for an unsupported SNMP version.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>6e06837ccf774ae59b71fe1ca31d47b7</uuid>
                    <name>snmpInBadCommunityNames</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.11.4.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.snmpInBadCommunityNames.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of community-based SNMP messages (for example, SNMPv1) delivered to the SNMP entity which used an SNMP community name not known to said entity. Also, implementations which authenticate community-based SNMP messages using check(s) in addition to matching the community name (for example, by also checking whether the message originated from a transport address allowed to use a specified community name) MAY include in this value the number of messages which failed the additional check(s). It is strongly RECOMMENDED that the documentation for any security model which is used to authenticate community-based SNMP messages specify the precise conditions that contribute to this value.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>a5bde1613a174c33ba9039ec3a3f1363</uuid>
                    <name>snmpInBadCommunityUses</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.11.5.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.snmpInBadCommunityUses.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of community-based SNMP messages (for example, SNMPv1) delivered to the SNMP entity which represented an SNMP operation that was not allowed for the SNMP community named in the message. The precise conditions under which this counter is incremented (if at all) depend on how the SNMP entity implements its access control mechanism and how its applications interact with that access control mechanism. It is strongly RECOMMENDED that the documentation for any access control mechanism which is used to control access to and visibility of MIB instrumentation specify the precise conditions that contribute to this value.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>7b814f70bffa4fec82023a4686004f46</uuid>
                    <name>snmpInASNParseErrs</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.11.6.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.snmpInASNParseErrs.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of ASN.1 or BER errors encountered by the SNMP entity when decoding received SNMP messages.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>620b139f965e47b99f9633b764dcfe12</uuid>
                    <name>snmpInTooBigs</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.11.8.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.snmpInTooBigs.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of SNMP PDUs which were delivered to the SNMP protocol entity and for which the value of the error-status field was `tooBig'.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>6a23f662f8fe43b7b5a30203e89ceddb</uuid>
                    <name>snmpInNoSuchNames</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.11.9.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.snmpInNoSuchNames.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of SNMP PDUs which were delivered to the SNMP protocol entity and for which the value of the error-status field was `noSuchName'.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>1282bb2bc37f472ab74be636bf827377</uuid>
                    <name>snmpInBadValues</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.11.10.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.snmpInBadValues.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of SNMP PDUs which were delivered to the SNMP protocol entity and for which the value of the error-status field was `badValue'.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>846052be529d4568b76c935506afc937</uuid>
                    <name>snmpInReadOnlys</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.11.11.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.snmpInReadOnlys.0</key>
                    <description>The total number valid SNMP PDUs which were delivered to the SNMP protocol entity and for which the value of the error-status field was `readOnly'. It should be noted that it is a protocol error to generate an SNMP PDU which contains the value `readOnly' in the error-status field, as such this object is provided as a means of detecting incorrect implementations of the SNMP.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>1923aa0c7bed450e878ea306b998ad4c</uuid>
                    <name>snmpInGenErrs</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.11.12.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.snmpInGenErrs.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of SNMP PDUs which were delivered to the SNMP protocol entity and for which the value of the error-status field was `genErr'.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>ea255e88ee7d4f12901db2818850a5b2</uuid>
                    <name>snmpInTotalReqVars</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.11.13.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.snmpInTotalReqVars.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of MIB objects which have been retrieved successfully by the SNMP protocol entity as the result of receiving valid SNMP Get-Request and Get-Next PDUs.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>2e305f93ccf649b797f8d6043afe7adb</uuid>
                    <name>snmpInTotalSetVars</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.11.14.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.snmpInTotalSetVars.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of MIB objects which have been altered successfully by the SNMP protocol entity as the result of receiving valid SNMP Set-Request PDUs.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>808ce728996041cc89df162590f13a73</uuid>
                    <name>snmpInGetRequests</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.11.15.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.snmpInGetRequests.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of SNMP Get-Request PDUs which have been accepted and processed by the SNMP protocol entity.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>0d435ace1d7a4d2e8cf52c92c862a110</uuid>
                    <name>snmpInGetNexts</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.11.16.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.snmpInGetNexts.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of SNMP Get-Next PDUs which have been accepted and processed by the SNMP protocol entity.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>3e6dba9ffe4b471b90921fa291130e51</uuid>
                    <name>snmpInSetRequests</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.11.17.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.snmpInSetRequests.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of SNMP Set-Request PDUs which have been accepted and processed by the SNMP protocol entity.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>00fa55f0b88649d592bb8d709af35f86</uuid>
                    <name>snmpInGetResponses</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.11.18.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.snmpInGetResponses.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of SNMP Get-Response PDUs which have been accepted and processed by the SNMP protocol entity.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>dcd28033aec040e5a8b3aa4b4b1359ec</uuid>
                    <name>snmpInTraps</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.11.19.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.snmpInTraps.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of SNMP Trap PDUs which have been accepted and processed by the SNMP protocol entity.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>5a14680683e44c14a6970b98e52cf595</uuid>
                    <name>snmpOutTooBigs</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.11.20.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.snmpOutTooBigs.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of SNMP PDUs which were generated by the SNMP protocol entity and for which the value of the error-status field was `tooBig.'</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>1d37682ead094d738d99e19d67f339cc</uuid>
                    <name>snmpOutNoSuchNames</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.11.21.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.snmpOutNoSuchNames.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of SNMP PDUs which were generated by the SNMP protocol entity and for which the value of the error-status was `noSuchName'.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>4b8172a8aa0c46f79eb401e29f02004b</uuid>
                    <name>snmpOutBadValues</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.11.22.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.snmpOutBadValues.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of SNMP PDUs which were generated by the SNMP protocol entity and for which the value of the error-status field was `badValue'.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>42c4438704c747bcb7ab0e40f9ce9186</uuid>
                    <name>snmpOutGenErrs</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.11.24.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.snmpOutGenErrs.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of SNMP PDUs which were generated by the SNMP protocol entity and for which the value of the error-status field was `genErr'.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>366ce13f87fc48338f07c10da50aa8da</uuid>
                    <name>snmpOutGetRequests</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.11.25.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.snmpOutGetRequests.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of SNMP Get-Request PDUs which have been generated by the SNMP protocol entity.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>8f54df706c9d47e7ae6cf5bc136d98e5</uuid>
                    <name>snmpOutGetNexts</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.11.26.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.snmpOutGetNexts.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of SNMP Get-Next PDUs which have been generated by the SNMP protocol entity.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>1072e44d955b455ca2a8432c04b0c564</uuid>
                    <name>snmpOutSetRequests</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.11.27.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.snmpOutSetRequests.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of SNMP Set-Request PDUs which have been generated by the SNMP protocol entity.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>47648a8fda504fb59777d8184d6b0e45</uuid>
                    <name>snmpOutGetResponses</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.11.28.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.snmpOutGetResponses.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of SNMP Get-Response PDUs which have been generated by the SNMP protocol entity.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>f61f1cbce9c04e99a3f993425d840790</uuid>
                    <name>snmpOutTraps</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.11.29.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.snmpOutTraps.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of SNMP Trap PDUs which have been generated by the SNMP protocol entity.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>6754d1b00e774e7991632f9e4ad87d89</uuid>
                    <name>snmpEnableAuthenTraps</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.11.30.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.snmpEnableAuthenTraps.0</key>                    
                    <value_type>FLOAT</value_type>
                    <description>Indicates whether the SNMP entity is permitted to generate authenticationFailure traps. The value of this object overrides any configuration information; as such, it provides a means whereby all authenticationFailure traps may be disabled. Note that it is strongly recommended that this object be stored in non-volatile memory so that it remains constant across re-initializations of the network management system.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>92eb786781ac428086d7d31a15e29c03</uuid>
                    <name>snmpSilentDrops</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.11.31.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.snmpSilentDrops.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of Confirmed Class PDUs (such as GetRequest-PDUs, GetNextRequest-PDUs, GetBulkRequest-PDUs, SetRequest-PDUs, and InformRequest-PDUs) delivered to the SNMP entity which were silently dropped because the size of a reply containing an alternate Response Class PDU (such as a Response-PDU) with an empty variable-bindings field was greater than either a local constraint or the maximum message size associated with the originator of the request.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>c9627ce5f1a54bd9bdb591232c826644</uuid>
                    <name>snmpProxyDrops</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.11.32.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.snmpProxyDrops.0</key>
                    <description>The total number of Confirmed Class PDUs (such as GetRequest-PDUs, GetNextRequest-PDUs, GetBulkRequest-PDUs, SetRequest-PDUs, and InformRequest-PDUs) delivered to the SNMP entity which were silently dropped because the transmission of the (possibly translated) message to a proxy target failed in a manner (other than a time-out) such that no Response Class PDU (such as a Response-PDU) could be returned.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>ffecd3f8b4be417693d862ce5e5fdf80</uuid>
                    <name>hrSystemUptime</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.25.1.1.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>HOST-RESOURCES-MIB.hrSystemUptime.0</key>
                    <description>The amount of time since this host was last initialized. Note that this is different from sysUpTime in the SNMPv2-MIB [RFC1907] because sysUpTime is the uptime of the network management portion of the system.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>fe75d4df34db40f88a98be0d9b9c789d</uuid>
                    <name>hrSystemDate</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.25.1.2.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>HOST-RESOURCES-MIB.hrSystemDate.0</key>                    
                    <value_type>CHAR</value_type>
                    <description>The host's notion of the local date and time of day.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>657d3a83840b47058a2fdde094dd762d</uuid>
                    <name>hrSystemInitialLoadDevice</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.25.1.3.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>HOST-RESOURCES-MIB.hrSystemInitialLoadDevice.0</key>                    
                    <value_type>FLOAT</value_type>
                    <description>The index of the hrDeviceEntry for the device from which this host is configured to load its initial operating system configuration (i.e., which operating system code and/or boot parameters). Note that writing to this object just changes the configuration that will be used the next time the operating system is loaded and does not actually cause the reload to occur.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>53060cc2409e4f18a802b7e7e2e3f751</uuid>
                    <name>hrSystemInitialLoadParameters</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.25.1.4.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>HOST-RESOURCES-MIB.hrSystemInitialLoadParameters.0</key>                    
                    <value_type>CHAR</value_type>
                    <description>This object contains the parameters (e.g. a pathname and parameter) supplied to the load device when requesting the initial operating system configuration from that device. Note that writing to this object just changes the configuration that will be used the next time the operating system is loaded and does not actually cause the reload to occur.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>b0b2877fb129403eafbaf8e0c91bdc46</uuid>
                    <name>hrSystemNumUsers</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.25.1.5.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>HOST-RESOURCES-MIB.hrSystemNumUsers.0</key>
                    <description>The number of user sessions for which this host is storing state information. A session is a collection of processes requiring a single act of user authentication and possibly subject to collective job control.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>02b79fae008a4e63b51813a17c488149</uuid>
                    <name>hrSystemProcesses</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.25.1.6.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>HOST-RESOURCES-MIB.hrSystemProcesses.0</key>
                    <description>The number of process contexts currently loaded or running on this system.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>97b2bc7aabce49aa86f1e4dadc2053fe</uuid>
                    <name>hrSystemMaxProcesses</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.25.1.7.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>HOST-RESOURCES-MIB.hrSystemMaxProcesses.0</key>                    
                    <value_type>FLOAT</value_type>
                    <description>The maximum number of process contexts this system can support. If there is no fixed maximum, the value should be zero. On systems that have a fixed maximum, this object can help diagnose failures that occur when this maximum is reached.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>8e076cefc2c64bcf8119700b6096d2d9</uuid>
                    <name>hrMemorySize</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.25.2.2.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>HOST-RESOURCES-MIB.hrMemorySize.0</key>                    
                    <value_type>FLOAT</value_type>
                    <description>The amount of physical read-write main memory, typically RAM, contained by the host.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>86ade87660b84463a134788a41e57749</uuid>
                    <name>ifTableLastChange</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.31.1.5.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IF-MIB.ifTableLastChange.0</key>
                    <description>The value of sysUpTime at the time of the last creation or deletion of an entry in the ifTable. If the number of entries has been unchanged since the last re-initialization of the local network management subsystem, then this object contains a zero value.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>02cb44fa468d4ec2897e9ad6a0cf9aa4</uuid>
                    <name>ipv6Forwarding</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.55.1.1.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IPV6-MIB.ipv6Forwarding.0</key>                    
                    <value_type>FLOAT</value_type>
                    <description>The indication of whether this entity is acting as an IPv6 router in respect to the forwarding of datagrams received by, but not addressed to, this entity. IPv6 routers forward datagrams. IPv6 hosts do not (except those source-routed via the host). Note that for some managed nodes, this object may take on only a subset of the values possible. Accordingly, it is appropriate for an agent to return a `wrongValue' response if a management station attempts to change this object to an inappropriate value.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>044955eb3f1b4dcea99ab954ef6ef8f1</uuid>
                    <name>ipv6DefaultHopLimit</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.55.1.2.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IPV6-MIB.ipv6DefaultHopLimit.0</key>                    
                    <value_type>FLOAT</value_type>
                    <description>The default value inserted into the Hop Limit field of the IPv6 header of datagrams originated at this entity, whenever a Hop Limit value is not supplied by the transport layer protocol.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>322473cbf1ac4b4aa693a3103f037025</uuid>
                    <name>ipv6Interfaces</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.55.1.3.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>IPV6-MIB.ipv6Interfaces.0</key>
                    <description>The number of IPv6 interfaces (regardless of their current state) present on this system.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>f91b61004cee4e8da8cbda02410116b0</uuid>
                    <name>mteResourceSampleMinimum</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.88.1.1.1.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>DISMAN-EVENT-MIB.mteResourceSampleMinimum.0</key>                    
                    <value_type>FLOAT</value_type>
                    <description>The minimum mteTriggerFrequency this system will accept. A system may use the larger values of this minimum to lessen the impact of constant sampling. For larger sampling intervals the system samples less often and suffers less overhead. This object provides a way to enforce such lower overhead for all triggers created after it is set. Unless explicitly resource limited, a system's value for this object SHOULD be 1, allowing as small as a 1 second interval for ongoing trigger sampling. Changing this value will not invalidate an existing setting of mteTriggerFrequency.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>4ef2c362bfa642d182e7128a962f812e</uuid>
                    <name>mteResourceSampleInstanceMaximum</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.88.1.1.2.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>DISMAN-EVENT-MIB.mteResourceSampleInstanceMaximum.0</key>
                    <description>The maximum number of instance entries this system will support for sampling. These are the entries that maintain state, one for each instance of each sampled object as selected by mteTriggerValueID. Note that wildcarded objects result in multiple instances of this state. A value of 0 indicates no preset limit, that is, the limit is dynamic based on system operation and resources. Unless explicitly resource limited, a system's value for this object SHOULD be 0. Changing this value will not eliminate or inhibit existing sample state but could prevent allocation of additional state information.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>87494e599a9840a4ba5764dc276c50c3</uuid>
                    <name>mteResourceSampleInstances</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.88.1.1.3.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>DISMAN-EVENT-MIB.mteResourceSampleInstances.0</key>
                    <description>The number of currently active instance entries as defined for mteResourceSampleInstanceMaximum.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>1abf9def9e844672937def591dad100c</uuid>
                    <name>mteResourceSampleInstancesHigh</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.88.1.1.4.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>DISMAN-EVENT-MIB.mteResourceSampleInstancesHigh.0</key>
                    <description>The highest value of mteResourceSampleInstances that has occurred since initialization of the management system.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>b0b02b407f7840168b0fde2cebf7840c</uuid>
                    <name>mteResourceSampleInstanceLacks</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.88.1.1.5.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>DISMAN-EVENT-MIB.mteResourceSampleInstanceLacks.0</key>
                    <description>The number of times this system could not take a new sample because that allocation would have exceeded the limit set by mteResourceSampleInstanceMaximum.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>5138cd20800349bf8c3f4fba0304f27b</uuid>
                    <name>mteTriggerFailures</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.88.1.2.1.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>DISMAN-EVENT-MIB.mteTriggerFailures.0</key>
                    <description>The number of times an attempt to check for a trigger condition has failed. This counts individually for each attempt in a group of targets or each attempt for a wildcarded object.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>fc859e32c12c44ed8d367b575b286428</uuid>
                    <name>nlmConfigGlobalEntryLimit</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.92.1.1.1.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>NOTIFICATION-LOG-MIB.nlmConfigGlobalEntryLimit.0</key>
                    <description>The maximum number of notification entries that may be held in nlmLogTable for all nlmLogNames added together. A particular setting does not guarantee that much data can be held. If an application changes the limit while there are Notifications in the log, the oldest Notifications MUST be discarded to bring the log down to the new limit - thus the value of nlmConfigGlobalEntryLimit MUST take precedence over the values of nlmConfigGlobalAgeOut and nlmConfigLogEntryLimit, even if the Notification being discarded has been present for fewer minutes than the value of nlmConfigGlobalAgeOut, or if the named log has fewer entries than that specified in nlmConfigLogEntryLimit. A value of 0 means no limit. Please be aware that contention between multiple managers trying to set this object to different values MAY affect the reliability and completeness of data seen by each manager.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>cd8b4055c66e4a9c801d96dc6909689d</uuid>
                    <name>nlmConfigGlobalAgeOut</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.92.1.1.2.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>NOTIFICATION-LOG-MIB.nlmConfigGlobalAgeOut.0</key>
                    <description>The number of minutes a Notification SHOULD be kept in a log before it is automatically removed. If an application changes the value of nlmConfigGlobalAgeOut, Notifications older than the new time MAY be discarded to meet the new time. A value of 0 means no age out. Please be aware that contention between multiple managers trying to set this object to different values MAY affect the reliability and completeness of data seen by each manager.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>dde05df8c329413e8df81bd65d56b30b</uuid>
                    <name>nlmStatsGlobalNotificationsLogged</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.92.1.2.1.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>NOTIFICATION-LOG-MIB.nlmStatsGlobalNotificationsLogged.0</key>
                    <description>The number of Notifications put into the nlmLogTable. This counts a Notification once for each log entry, so a Notification put into multiple logs is counted multiple times.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>                  
                <item>
                    <uuid>b5ea63a92c114668b82a23b0d02bc6a2</uuid>
                    <name>nlmStatsGlobalNotificationsBumped</name>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.92.1.2.2.0</snmp_oid>
                    <key>NOTIFICATION-LOG-MIB.nlmStatsGlobalNotificationsBumped.0</key>
                    <description>The number of log entries discarded to make room for a new entry due to lack of resources or the value of nlmConfigGlobalEntryLimit or nlmConfigLogEntryLimit. This does not include entries discarded due to the value of nlmConfigGlobalAgeOut.</description>
                    <history>7d</history>
                    <trends>0</trends>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                </item>
            </items>
            <discovery_rules>
                <discovery_rule>
                    <uuid>7dd6ba1c77a14f6b9040e4d78d96be18</uuid>
                    <name>sysORTable</name>
                    <delay>3600</delay>
                    <key>SNMPv2-MIB.sysORTable</key>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <item_prototypes>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>20748f57700a4ae49562600881007b76</uuid>
                            <name>sysORID.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.1.9.1.2.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.1.9.1.2.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>                    
                            <value_type>CHAR</value_type>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>An authoritative identification of a capabilities statement with respect to various MIB modules supported by the local SNMP application acting as a command responder.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>58474ff255dc4eeba5b94100763d4651</uuid>
                            <name>sysORDescr.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.1.9.1.3.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.1.9.1.3.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>                    
                            <value_type>CHAR</value_type>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>A textual description of the capabilities identified by the corresponding instance of sysORID.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>34af545a4e874fa1831bac3cf1f0f971</uuid>
                            <name>sysORUpTime.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.1.9.1.4.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.1.9.1.4.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>The value of sysUpTime at the time this conceptual row was last instantiated.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>                        
                    </item_prototypes>
                    <snmp_oid>discovery[{#SYSORID},.1.3.6.1.2.1.1.9.1.2,{#SYSORDESCR},.1.3.6.1.2.1.1.9.1.3,{#SYSORUPTIME},.1.3.6.1.2.1.1.9.1.4]</snmp_oid>
                </discovery_rule>
                <discovery_rule>
                    <uuid>270c8d9892ea410d82c386d896869140</uuid>
                    <name>ifTable</name>
                    <delay>3600</delay>
                    <key>IF-MIB.ifTable</key>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <item_prototypes>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>d67b64282e634951a085f4a41114d413</uuid>
                            <name>ifIndex.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.1.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.1.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>                    
                            <value_type>FLOAT</value_type>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>A unique value, greater than zero, for each interface. It is recommended that values are assigned contiguously starting from 1. The value for each interface sub-layer must remain constant at least from one re-initialization of the entity's network management system to the next re- initialization.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>a47fcef2c4254a8093c7df36fb9214cd</uuid>
                            <name>ifDescr.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.2.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.2.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>                    
                            <value_type>CHAR</value_type>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>A textual string containing information about the interface. This string should include the name of the manufacturer, the product name and the version of the interface hardware/software.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>b705cf02ab634c6594c63aee289b4929</uuid>
                            <name>ifType.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.3.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.3.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>                    
                            <value_type>FLOAT</value_type>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>The type of interface. Additional values for ifType are assigned by the Internet Assigned Numbers Authority (IANA), through updating the syntax of the IANAifType textual convention.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>8983176bd9ce42419f83638dd9c5743c</uuid>
                            <name>ifMtu.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.4.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.4.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>                    
                            <value_type>FLOAT</value_type>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>The size of the largest packet which can be sent/received on the interface, specified in octets. For interfaces that are used for transmitting network datagrams, this is the size of the largest network datagram that can be sent on the interface.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>f950fd51830246bebe4b7b5191fb0c71</uuid>
                            <name>ifSpeed.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.5.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.5.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>An estimate of the interface's current bandwidth in bits per second. For interfaces which do not vary in bandwidth or for those where no accurate estimation can be made, this object should contain the nominal bandwidth. If the bandwidth of the interface is greater than the maximum value reportable by this object then this object should report its maximum value (4,294,967,295) and ifHighSpeed must be used to report the interace's speed. For a sub-layer which has no concept of bandwidth, this object should be zero.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>42bc84dcbb3a4314a659086ffc07bd95</uuid>
                            <name>ifPhysAddress.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.6.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.6.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>                    
                            <value_type>CHAR</value_type>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>The interface's address at its protocol sub-layer. For example, for an 802.x interface, this object normally contains a MAC address. The interface's media-specific MIB must define the bit and byte ordering and the format of the value of this object. For interfaces which do not have such an address (e.g., a serial line), this object should contain an octet string of zero length.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>5560ece9fc15402aae84e90b6bcc2915</uuid>
                            <name>ifAdminStatus.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.7.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.7.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>                    
                            <value_type>FLOAT</value_type>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>The desired state of the interface. The testing(3) state indicates that no operational packets can be passed. When a managed system initializes, all interfaces start with ifAdminStatus in the down(2) state. As a result of either explicit management action or per configuration information retained by the managed system, ifAdminStatus is then changed to either the up(1) or testing(3) states (or remains in the down(2) state).</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>705e4e5af2c545708f10cb9f817c6126</uuid>
                            <name>ifOperStatus.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.8.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.8.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>                    
                            <value_type>FLOAT</value_type>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>The current operational state of the interface. The testing(3) state indicates that no operational packets can be passed. If ifAdminStatus is down(2) then ifOperStatus should be down(2). If ifAdminStatus is changed to up(1) then ifOperStatus should change to up(1) if the interface is ready to transmit and receive network traffic; it should change to dormant(5) if the interface is waiting for external actions (such as a serial line waiting for an incoming connection); it should remain in the down(2) state if and only if there is a fault that prevents it from going to the up(1) state; it should remain in the notPresent(6) state if the interface has missing (typically, hardware) components.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>49634126594a4bb388d875933b426c96</uuid>
                            <name>ifLastChange.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.9.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.9.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>The value of sysUpTime at the time the interface entered its current operational state. If the current state was entered prior to the last re-initialization of the local network management subsystem, then this object contains a zero value.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>275e8faa732a478d87a8c80539bd0460</uuid>
                            <name>ifInOctets.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.10.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.10.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>The total number of octets received on the interface, including framing characters. Discontinuities in the value of this counter can occur at re-initialization of the management system, and at other times as indicated by the value of ifCounterDiscontinuityTime.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>e71e82b5edb54c609b7eed3daa1843c8</uuid>
                            <name>ifInUcastPkts.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.11.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.11.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>The number of packets, delivered by this sub-layer to a higher (sub-)layer, which were not addressed to a multicast or broadcast address at this sub-layer. Discontinuities in the value of this counter can occur at re-initialization of the management system, and at other times as indicated by the value of ifCounterDiscontinuityTime.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>e55504b31b1a46509ee383796fbc5f21</uuid>
                            <name>ifInNUcastPkts.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.12.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.12.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>The number of packets, delivered by this sub-layer to a higher (sub-)layer, which were addressed to a multicast or broadcast address at this sub-layer. Discontinuities in the value of this counter can occur at re-initialization of the management system, and at other times as indicated by the value of ifCounterDiscontinuityTime. This object is deprecated in favour of ifInMulticastPkts and ifInBroadcastPkts.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>d4465b1986384d37b995e832cff73100</uuid>
                            <name>ifInDiscards.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.13.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.13.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>The number of inbound packets which were chosen to be discarded even though no errors had been detected to prevent their being deliverable to a higher-layer protocol. One possible reason for discarding such a packet could be to free up buffer space. Discontinuities in the value of this counter can occur at re-initialization of the management system, and at other times as indicated by the value of ifCounterDiscontinuityTime.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>c1fe9bb5caa8467b96bdd30b37056b7d</uuid>
                            <name>ifInErrors.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.14.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.14.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>For packet-oriented interfaces, the number of inbound packets that contained errors preventing them from being deliverable to a higher-layer protocol. For character- oriented or fixed-length interfaces, the number of inbound transmission units that contained errors preventing them from being deliverable to a higher-layer protocol. Discontinuities in the value of this counter can occur at re-initialization of the management system, and at other times as indicated by the value of ifCounterDiscontinuityTime.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>e20411fda8c84c7fa68d5ee6fa36717e</uuid>
                            <name>ifInUnknownProtos.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.15.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.15.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>For packet-oriented interfaces, the number of packets received via the interface which were discarded because of an unknown or unsupported protocol. For character-oriented or fixed-length interfaces that support protocol multiplexing the number of transmission units received via the interface which were discarded because of an unknown or unsupported protocol. For any interface that does not support protocol multiplexing, this counter will always be 0. Discontinuities in the value of this counter can occur at re-initialization of the management system, and at other times as indicated by the value of ifCounterDiscontinuityTime.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>57f736756e1d4277bc04173a21ba623f</uuid>
                            <name>ifOutOctets.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.16.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.16.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>The total number of octets transmitted out of the interface, including framing characters. Discontinuities in the value of this counter can occur at re-initialization of the management system, and at other times as indicated by the value of ifCounterDiscontinuityTime.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>10a39da0c2da44d0ba4054ecd2142a3a</uuid>
                            <name>ifOutUcastPkts.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.17.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.17.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>The total number of packets that higher-level protocols requested be transmitted, and which were not addressed to a multicast or broadcast address at this sub-layer, including those that were discarded or not sent. Discontinuities in the value of this counter can occur at re-initialization of the management system, and at other times as indicated by the value of ifCounterDiscontinuityTime.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>30605d3dfb714daeb7d18ce5adb38f49</uuid>
                            <name>ifOutNUcastPkts.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.18.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.18.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>The total number of packets that higher-level protocols requested be transmitted, and which were addressed to a multicast or broadcast address at this sub-layer, including those that were discarded or not sent. Discontinuities in the value of this counter can occur at re-initialization of the management system, and at other times as indicated by the value of ifCounterDiscontinuityTime. This object is deprecated in favour of ifOutMulticastPkts and ifOutBroadcastPkts.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>c92fef2401d34ac194fdc1c9f358dfc1</uuid>
                            <name>ifOutDiscards.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.19.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.19.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>The number of outbound packets which were chosen to be discarded even though no errors had been detected to prevent their being transmitted. One possible reason for discarding such a packet could be to free up buffer space. Discontinuities in the value of this counter can occur at re-initialization of the management system, and at other times as indicated by the value of ifCounterDiscontinuityTime.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>1904d7a8efc54b0ebb41788a55b88be4</uuid>
                            <name>ifOutErrors.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.20.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.20.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>For packet-oriented interfaces, the number of outbound packets that could not be transmitted because of errors. For character-oriented or fixed-length interfaces, the number of outbound transmission units that could not be transmitted because of errors. Discontinuities in the value of this counter can occur at re-initialization of the management system, and at other times as indicated by the value of ifCounterDiscontinuityTime.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>e1551a7583304843b1cc460d0542f328</uuid>
                            <name>ifOutQLen.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.21.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.21.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>The length of the output packet queue (in packets).</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>4cb2c7408f73463cb214a117592a2474</uuid>
                            <name>ifSpecific.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.22.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.22.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>                    
                            <value_type>CHAR</value_type>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>A reference to MIB definitions specific to the particular media being used to realize the interface. It is recommended that this value point to an instance of a MIB object in the media-specific MIB, i.e., that this object have the semantics associated with the InstancePointer textual convention defined in RFC 2579. In fact, it is recommended that the media-specific MIB specify what value ifSpecific should/can take for values of ifType. If no MIB definitions specific to the particular media are available, the value should be set to the OBJECT IDENTIFIER { 0 0 }.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>                        
                    </item_prototypes>
                    <snmp_oid>discovery[{#IFINDEX},.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.1,{#IFDESCR},.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.2,{#IFTYPE},.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.3,{#IFMTU},.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.4,{#IFSPEED},.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.5,{#IFPHYSADDRESS},.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.6,{#IFADMINSTATUS},.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.7,{#IFOPERSTATUS},.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.8,{#IFLASTCHANGE},.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.9,{#IFINOCTETS},.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.10,{#IFINUCASTPKTS},.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.11,{#IFINNUCASTPKTS},.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.12,{#IFINDISCARDS},.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.13,{#IFINERRORS},.1.3.6.1.2.1.2.2.1.14]</snmp_oid>
                </discovery_rule>
                <discovery_rule>
                    <uuid>154f0c4d633a497c8fb237f06a1feff4</uuid>
                    <name>ipv6ScopeZoneIndexTable</name>
                    <delay>3600</delay>
                    <key>IP-MIB.ipv6ScopeZoneIndexTable</key>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <item_prototypes>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>a47d90fb1a50405e9477ef53e54aca6a</uuid>
                            <name>ipv6ScopeZoneIndexLinkLocal.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.36.1.2.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.36.1.2.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>The zone index for the link-local scope on this interface.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>e50330dd26b94b3a80cd54bb224ae1a6</uuid>
                            <name>ipv6ScopeZoneIndex3.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.36.1.3.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.36.1.3.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>The zone index for scope 3 on this interface.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>634f855bbb6e49b19e15224dd7a95803</uuid>
                            <name>ipv6ScopeZoneIndexAdminLocal.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.36.1.4.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.36.1.4.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>The zone index for the admin-local scope on this interface.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>ebfa7b63e242426aa14e72b26bf3c105</uuid>
                            <name>ipv6ScopeZoneIndexSiteLocal.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.36.1.5.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.36.1.5.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>The zone index for the site-local scope on this interface.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>be5ab2f70f8d40878a5d5980ac9415ea</uuid>
                            <name>ipv6ScopeZoneIndex6.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.36.1.6.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.36.1.6.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>The zone index for scope 6 on this interface.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>8ad21d39f0334493a90c9bbfc412d470</uuid>
                            <name>ipv6ScopeZoneIndex7.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.36.1.7.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.36.1.7.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>The zone index for scope 7 on this interface.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>6c59983a172f49b888594ead2201d807</uuid>
                            <name>ipv6ScopeZoneIndexOrganizationLocal.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.36.1.8.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.36.1.8.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>The zone index for the organization-local scope on this interface.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>8bd3bfd26cd34a5c8620e436491ea1ba</uuid>
                            <name>ipv6ScopeZoneIndex9.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.36.1.9.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.36.1.9.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>The zone index for scope 9 on this interface.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>cb14b86a3458414b9455bdc050026576</uuid>
                            <name>ipv6ScopeZoneIndexA.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.36.1.10.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.36.1.10.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>The zone index for scope A on this interface.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>2de28d67a6dd4264a72ff08e912f31c2</uuid>
                            <name>ipv6ScopeZoneIndexB.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.36.1.11.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.36.1.11.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>The zone index for scope B on this interface.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>68be15c18e574e158fe47b15f87c522c</uuid>
                            <name>ipv6ScopeZoneIndexC.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.36.1.12.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.36.1.12.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>The zone index for scope C on this interface.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>53284118d0494501b994d5338c831cd1</uuid>
                            <name>ipv6ScopeZoneIndexD.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.36.1.13.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.36.1.13.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>The zone index for scope D on this interface.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>                        
                    </item_prototypes>
                    <snmp_oid>discovery[{#IPV6SCOPEZONEINDEXLINKLOCAL},.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.36.1.2,{#IPV6SCOPEZONEINDEX3},.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.36.1.3,{#IPV6SCOPEZONEINDEXADMINLOCAL},.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.36.1.4,{#IPV6SCOPEZONEINDEXSITELOCAL},.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.36.1.5,{#IPV6SCOPEZONEINDEX6},.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.36.1.6,{#IPV6SCOPEZONEINDEX7},.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.36.1.7,{#IPV6SCOPEZONEINDEXORGANIZATIONLOCAL},.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.36.1.8,{#IPV6SCOPEZONEINDEX9},.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.36.1.9,{#IPV6SCOPEZONEINDEXA},.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.36.1.10,{#IPV6SCOPEZONEINDEXB},.1.3.6.1.2.1.4.36.1.11]</snmp_oid>
                </discovery_rule>
                <discovery_rule>
                    <uuid>3ae082032ad24ade8dc8ede16fe1b05c</uuid>
                    <name>icmpStatsTable</name>
                    <delay>3600</delay>
                    <key>IP-MIB.icmpStatsTable</key>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <item_prototypes>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>8fa5aa63d7684a788d658a40c7350c2a</uuid>
                            <name>icmpStatsInMsgs.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.29.1.2.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.29.1.2.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>The total number of ICMP messages that the entity received. Note that this counter includes all those counted by icmpStatsInErrors.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>33738f7034504b2b94e4cbe3a0f92250</uuid>
                            <name>icmpStatsInErrors.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.29.1.3.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.29.1.3.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>The number of ICMP messages that the entity received but determined as having ICMP-specific errors (bad ICMP checksums, bad length, etc.).</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>480fefab9a96466db675142bb9511877</uuid>
                            <name>icmpStatsOutMsgs.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.29.1.4.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.29.1.4.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>The total number of ICMP messages that the entity attempted to send. Note that this counter includes all those counted by icmpStatsOutErrors.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>dd684b245107431695f0a7b197531048</uuid>
                            <name>icmpStatsOutErrors.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.29.1.5.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.29.1.5.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>The number of ICMP messages that this entity did not send due to problems discovered within ICMP, such as a lack of buffers. This value should not include errors discovered outside the ICMP layer, such as the inability of IP to route the resultant datagram. In some implementations, there may be no types of error that contribute to this counter's value.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>                        
                    </item_prototypes>
                    <snmp_oid>discovery[{#ICMPSTATSINMSGS},.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.29.1.2,{#ICMPSTATSINERRORS},.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.29.1.3,{#ICMPSTATSOUTMSGS},.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.29.1.4,{#ICMPSTATSOUTERRORS},.1.3.6.1.2.1.5.29.1.5]</snmp_oid>
                </discovery_rule>
                <discovery_rule>
                    <uuid>740988a44a284aae823d993518ead974</uuid>
                    <name>mtaTable</name>
                    <delay>3600</delay>
                    <key>MTA-MIB.mtaTable</key>
                    <status>DISABLED</status>
                    <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                    <item_prototypes>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>a2353a0e18a84b76a4659207b0bf10c2</uuid>
                            <name>mtaStoredMessages.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.28.1.1.2.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.28.1.1.2.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>The total number of messages currently stored in the MTA. This includes messages that are awaiting transmission to some other MTA or are waiting for delivery to an end-user or application.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>
                        <item_prototype>
                            <uuid>d9cbb0e8a396464db776b3e89cc7e89c</uuid>
                            <name>mtaStoredVolume.{#SNMPINDEX}</name>
                            <type>SNMP_AGENT</type>
                            <snmp_oid>.1.3.6.1.2.1.28.1.1.5.{#SNMPINDEX}</snmp_oid>
                            <key>.1.3.6.1.2.1.28.1.1.5.[{#SNMPINDEX}]</key>
                            <delay>1h</delay>
                            <history>7d</history>
                            <description>The total volume of messages currently stored in the MTA, measured in kilo-octets. This volume should include all stored data that is logically above the mail transport protocol level. For example, an SMTP-based MTA should use the number of kilo-octets in the message header and body, while an X.400-based MTA would use the number of kilo-octets of P2 data. This includes messages that are awaiting transmission to some other MTA or are waiting for delivery to an end-user or application.</description>                           
                        </item_prototype>                        
                    </item_prototypes>
                    <snmp_oid>discovery[{#MTASTOREDMESSAGES},.1.3.6.1.2.1.28.1.1.2,{#MTASTOREDVOLUME},.1.3.6.1.2.1.28.1.1.5]</snmp_oid>
                </discovery_rule>
            </discovery_rules>
        </template>
    </templates>
</zabbix_export>